const STORE = {
  currentQuestion: 0,
  score: 0,
  page: "Landing Page", 
  questions: [//1
      {
        question: 'What is the strongest material in the MCU?',
        options: [
          "Proto-Adamantium", 
          "Kryptonite", 
          "Vibranium", 
          "Enchanted uru",
          "None of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "Proto-Adamantium"
      },
      //2
      {
        question: 'What is the real name of Black Widow?',
        options: [
          "Vanessa Valalski",
          "Natalia Romanova", 
          "Natasha Romanoff",
          "Scarlett Johansson",
          "None of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "Natasha Romanoff"
      },
      //3
      {
        question: 'In which film do we finally learn the backstory behind how Nick Fury lost his eye?',
        options: [
          "Captain America: The Winter Soldier", 
          "Ironman 1", 
          "Captain America: Civil War", 
          "Captain Marvel",
          "None of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "Captain Marvel"
      },
      //4
      {
        question: "What is Deadpool's favorite food?", 
        options: ["Cheeseburger", "Chimichangas", "Pizza", "Pancakes", "None of the Above"],
        answer: "Chimichangas"
      },
      //5
      {
        question: "What is the name of the axe created for and then used by Thor in Avengers: Infinity War?",
        options: [
          "Windwrecker", 
          "Mjolnir", 
          "Gungnir", 
          "Stormbreaker",
          "None of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "Stormbreaker"
      },
      //6
      {
        question: "What is the infamous villian in the next Venom movie?",
        options: [
          "Carnage", 
          "Sandman", 
          "Lizard", 
          "Doctor Octopus",
          "None of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "Carnage"
      },
      //7
      {
        question: "What song do we hear first in Guardians of the Galaxy?",
        options: [
          "Come and Get Your Love by Redbone", 
          "Bring It On Home to Me by Sam Cooke", 
          "I'm Not In Love by 10cc", 
          "Don't Stop Me Now by Queen",
          "None of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "I'm Not In Love by 10cc"
      },
      //8
      {
        question: "How many Iron Man movies are there?", 
        options: [
          "5", 
          "4", 
          "3", 
          "2",
          "None of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "3"
      },
      //9
      {
        question: "What MCU movie starring Jared Leto is supposed to release this year?",
        options: [
          "Blade", 
          "Punisher", 
          "Suicide Squad", 
          "Morbius",
          "None of the Above"
        ], 
        answer: "Morbius"
      },
      //10
      {
        question: "How does the character Blade become half-vampire?",
        options: [
          "His mother was bitten by a vampire when giving birth", 
          "Was given vampire blood ritually", 
          "Was bitten by a vampire passing on vampire enzymes", 
          "He made a deal with Dracula",
          "None of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "His mother was bitten by a vampire when giving birth"
      },
      //11
      {
        question: "In what film's post-credit scene did Thanos first appear?",
        options: [
          "Avengers", 
          "Avengers: Age of Ultron", 
          "Ironman 2",
          "Ironman 3", 
          "None of the above"
        ],
        answer: 'Avengers: Age of Ultron'
      },
      //12
      {
        question: "What is the species does Loki originally hail?", 
        options: [
          "Asgardian", 
          "Frost Giants", 
          "Demon", 
          "Vanir",
          "None of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "Frost Giants"
      },
      //13
      {
        question: "Who is the villain in Spiderman: Far From Home?",
        options: [
          "Lizard", 
          "Green Goblin", 
          "Doctor Octopus", 
          "Mysterio",
          "None of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "Mysterio"
      },
      //14
      {
        question: "Who is the voice of Rocket?",
        options: [
          "Brad Pitt", 
          "Bradley Cooper", 
          "Vin Diesel",
          "Morgan Freeman", 
          "None of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "Bradley Cooper"
      },
      //15
      {
        question: "What did Yondu refer to himself in the last Guardians of the Galaxy?",
        options: [
          "Mary Poppins", 
          "A space pirate", 
          "A straight shooter",
          "A good for nothing scoundrel", 
          "All of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "Mary Poppins"
      }
    ],
  };